>> Brian Holt: 如果您还没有，请克隆 GitHub 存储库。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I need you to, if you
haven't already, go clone the GitHub repo.
所以如果你做了 " 雷法" 的完整简介
So if you've taken
the complete intro to React,
很明显我在修理修理公司的码头上
obviously what I have in
the docs in the repo is going to
与我在课程中所写的内容有很大的不同
differ very slightly from what I've
actually written in the course.
因为有些写在苍蝇上面有问题
Because some of that's written on the fly,
and there's questions and
如此来来去
so on and so forth.
所以我要开始一个全新的，干净的雷波克隆。
So I'm actually just gonna start with
a fresh, clean clone of the repo.
所以我要说， >> Brian Holt: 在这里，
So I'm gonna say,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Right here,
获取克隆 git@gitHub.com.btholt 。
get clone git@gitHub.com.btholt this.
>> Brian Holt: 您可以通过转至 repo，克隆或
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You can get this URL as
well just by going to the repo, clone or
下载，复制该屏幕按钮，在此处克隆或下载。
download, copy that,
the screen button here clone or download.
> > Brian Holt: 然后，我要去做这个，然后把它贴在那里，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then, I'm gonna go
into this and then paste that there,
把它克隆好吗
git clone that, okay?
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 好的，然后我要去找我刚克隆的
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and then I'm going to
go into the repo that I just cloned and
我要说 npm 的安装
I'm going to say npm install.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 在你的每一个时间，大概都是个好主意
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So probably a good idea
every single time that you go from
模块，用于在此之后进行模块。
module to module after this.
如果您要克隆新的存储库，或者
To you can just either clone
a new repo if you want to or
至少要再次运行 npm 安装，直至您。
at least run an npm install again,
up to you.
>> Brian Holt: 好， >> Brian Holt: 因此
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
我要在密码里打开这个
I'm gonna open this in code.
>> Brian Holt: 所以让我们来了解一下这个项目
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So let's just get you
acquainted with this project really
啊，快啊。
quickly.
我就在这里做密码
I'll just do it here from code.
如果你去看你的容器 .json， >> Brian Holt:
If you go look in your package.json,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's
用包裹来建造这个
using parcel to build this.
这是一个 React 项目，它有 ESLint 和 Pretier 。
It's a React project, it has ESLint and
Prettier built into it.
如果你对这些事有疑问的话
If you have questions about
any of these things, again,
请参阅 " 追溯 " 。
refer to the intro to React.
它有一个前端主控/宠物客户端，这将使 API 请求
It has a frontendmasters/pet client,
which will make API requests for
你可以看到动物收养
you to see animals to adopt.
它也使用了 roach/router 。
And it uses reach/router, as well.
在下面，您可以看到您有一些要使用的脚本。
Down here you can see that
you have some scripts to use.
这里有一个如果你出于任何原因需要清理建筑
So one of these here, if you need to clear
the build cache for whatever reason,
此处有明确的构建高速缓存功能，将除去该功能。
there is a clear build cache
function here that will remove that.
有一个设备将运行此项目。
There is a dev thing which
will run this project.
因此，如果我打开我的客户端，请说 npm 运行 dev。
So if I open my client right on,
say npm run dev.
它将开始运行我可以访问的开发者服务器。
It'll start running the developer
server that I can reach that.
如果出于任何原因您处于脱机状态，或者
If for whatever reason you're offline, or
我们的 API 不像你期待的那样，你可以做鬼鬼子。
our API isn't working the way that you're
expecting it to, you can do dev:mock.
所以就像这个，呜， npm 跑 : 模拟。
So like this, whoops, npm run dev:mock.
这将以模拟方式运行 API 客户机，
And this will run the API
client in mock mode,
这意味着你将会得到假数据它不会出去的
which means that you'll be getting
fake data and it won't be going out.
所以如果你在火车上观看这些视频
So if you're on the train
watching these videos offline,
感谢前端主控服务器执行脱机视频。
thanks Front End Masters for
doing offline videos.
实际上，您可以脱机运行此客户机，并且
You can actually run
this client offline and
整个项目都下线了，这很酷。
the entire project works offline,
which is cool.
好，您可以运行 npm，运行格式，该格式将格式化所有与 Pretier的格式。
Okay, you can run npm, run format which
will format everything with Prettier.
然后我最喜欢的就是现在的测试
And lint it, and then my favorite
are the existing tests that if you
send npm run test" 它说，日志没有测试， [LAUGH] 正确。
send npm run test" it says,
log there are no tests, [LAUGH] right.
没有指定测试，在那里。
No test specified, right there.
就这样了，所以现在我要用 npm 的方式来运行，就像这样。
That's it, so right now I'm gonna run
this in npm run dev mode, like that.
这将在 1234上打开一个开发服务器。
And this will open
a development server on 1234.
>> Brian Holt: 最终，我们开始。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Eventually, there we go.
>> Brian Holt: 这是我们一起构建的项目
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And this is the project
that we built together in the complete
intro，对吧 ?
intro, right?
因此，在书面结果中，它的位置在西雅图。
So as of writing results,
it's location is in Seattle.
所以如果我在这里提交，这将会打开这些特定的动物。
So if I submit here,
this will open these particular animals.
现在这两处地方都是西雅图
The only two locations this
works in right now is Seattle,
华盛顿和旧金山加利福尼亚
Washington and San Francisco California.
我们会在每一个地点工作
We'll work to make this work
in every location, but for
现在只在这两个地方工作
now it's only working
in these two locations.
我去看看西奥你很可爱
I'll look at Theo, you're adorable.
>> Brian Holt: 在这里，您可以单击 " Theo" 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And so
here you can click adopt Theo.
如果您单击 " 是" ，
If you click Yes,
它会带你到领养的地方
it'll actually take you to the adoption
page where you can adopt Theo.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So go back.
>> Brian Holt: 然后您可以选择，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then you can select,
如果你从狗到马， >> Brian Holt: 你可以
if you move from dog to horse,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You can
看它改变了马的微风
see it changes the breeds of
the horses like miniature
马， >> Brian Holt: Like Gidget。
horses,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Like Gidget.
>> Brian Holt: 然后您也可以更改应用程序的主题。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then you can change
the theme of your application as well.